® DESCRIPTION OF FILE

Description of File (In accordance with Finnish Personal Data Act, section 10)

Name of the Data File

Customer register

Name and Address of the Data Controller

Codebay Oy
PL 63
02601 Espoo
Finland

(Visiting address: Codebay Oy, Tekniikantie 14 (Innopoli 2), 02600 Espoo, Finland.)

Purpose of the Processing of the Personal Data

Customer service, delivery and billing of products, development of products and services

Description of Data Groups and Collected Information

Customers, data collected:

Name
User name
Country of location
E-mail address
Unique identification number (customer number)
Credit card identification data

Disclose and Transfer of Data

No data is disclosed to third parties or transferred outside European Union except for credit card billing data of foreign customers as requested by customers ordering products.

Description of Security Principles

Data file is stored in Finland in a way that it is protected from unauthorized access or use (by using passwords and encryption).

Rights of the Registered Persons

A registered person shall have the right of access, after having supplied sufficient search criteria, to the data on him/her in a personal data file, or to a notice that the file contains no such data. This is done without cost once a year. A request to this effect to the controller shall be made by a personally signed or otherwise comparably verified document or by appearing personally in the premises of the controller.

A registered person has the right to request the data controller to rectify, erase or supplement personal data contained in its personal data file and rectify erroneous, unnecessary, incomplete or obsolete data as regards the purpose of the processing and prohibit the controller to process personal data for purposes of direct advertising.

Copyright © Codebay Oy 2007. Codebay® and VPNease® are registered trademarks of Codebay Oy.

Document last updated: 27.8.2007.

® LEGAL NOTICE

Legal Notice

This website is owned by Codebay Oy (hereinafter the "Website"). The following terms and conditions shall apply to any and all use of this Website.

All use of the Website contrary to these terms and conditions is prohibited. If you do not accept these terms and conditions, you are not allowed to use this Website.

Click here to learn about our privacy policy.

General Terms of Use

Codebay Oy reserves all rights to this Website and its contents. Unless otherwise expressly stated in these terms and conditions, a user of the Website has no right to copy, even partially (including mirroring), or otherwise replicate, save, move, forward, distribute, publish, include into other material, or in any way download to one's own computer any material from the Website (including any text, pictures, trademarks, logos, graphics or music) without the express written consent of Codebay Oy.

Separate terms of use respective to the products, goods or services offered on or through the Website may be applicable. Separate license terms apply to all software offered on or through the Website.

The Finnish law is applied to the terms of use of the Website.

Permitted Use

Any written material and content on the Website may only be used (including necessary copying), if a) the source of the material is stated appropriately and copyright notices are included in all copies made, b) the use of the material is private and non-commercial only, c) no material taken from the Website is altered in any way.

All other use without the express prior written consent of Codebay Oy is strictly prohibited. A violation of the prohibition can result in legal action and liability for damages. A violation of these terms and conditions automatically leads to termination of all rights to use the Website.

Copyright and Trademarks

The Website is the property of Codebay Oy.

The copyright and other rights to all content on the Website and its appearance (including all information and written material, e-documents, graphics, pictures and sounds, software, software products and services) are the property of Codebay Oy or third parties. All trademarks, product marks, business and company signs and other equivalent material on the Website are the property of Codebay Oy or a third party. The pages are protected by the Copyright Act, the Trademarks Act and international copyright treaties.

Codebay® and VPNease® are registered trademarks of Codebay Oy.

Software

Any software offered to users on the Website against payment or free of charge is the property of Codebay Oy or third parties, and respective copyrights and other rights are the property of Codebay Oy and/or third parties. Unless otherwise expressly stated herein, all software programs are intended for their end-users only. License terms and conditions of Codebay Oy or third parties (as applicable) shall apply to any and all software available via the Website.

User must agree to any applicable license terms and conditions before using the software or downloading it. All copying, duplicating, saving, changing, transferring, distributing, publishing, including into other material and other equivalent activity is strictly prohibited, unless otherwise expressly stated in the applicable license terms and conditions.

Codebay Oy does not give any guarantee whatsoever to any software available through the Website unless otherwise stated in the applicable license terms and conditions.

No Liability

Codebay Oy is the publisher of the Website and any material thereon. Codebay Oy is not responsible for the availability, reliability, faultlessness, fitness for any specific purpose, the use or non-use or any other matter of the Website, its contents and other material thereon, or any products, goods or services offered through the Website, unless otherwise expressly stated in these terms and conditions or otherwise stated respectively of the products, goods, services and materials.

The user of the Website shall under any and all circumstances be responsible for the maintenance of his computer and communications hardware, their use, condition, security, the making of backups, virus protection, and other corresponding activities. Codebay Oy is under no circumstances liable for any possible direct or indirect damages suffered by the user of the Website for any reason. The user of the Website is liable for all damages caused intentionally or by negligence (for example by spreading computer viruses or endangering information security) to Codebay Oy or a third party to their full extent.

Codebay Oy will make reasonable efforts to administer and publish the Website with adequate technology in accordance with good information security practices. Codebay Oy is, however, not liable for any technical or other malfunction or a threat thereof caused by the use of the Website to the user or any other party.

Right to Change Reserved

The Website is provided "as is". Codebay Oy does not guarantee the functioning or availability of the Website or any content thereof. Codebay Oy has, at any time, the right to update, change, add or remove any material on the Website and restrict access to the Website without prior notice. Codebay Oy has the right, at any time and without prior notice, to change the terms of use of the Website, the selection and contents of the products, goods and services available on the Website and any possible applicable license terms and terms of use in addition to the appearance, contents and other properties of the Website.

The Providing of Material

The user of the Website assures, and is responsible for that no illegal or otherwise inappropriate material is sent by the user to the Website. The user must ensure that the material being sent does not contain any computer viruses or be harmful in any other way. Codebay Oy has the right, at any time and without prior notice to remove and destroy any material provided to the Website or to Codebay Oy through the Website.

Codebay Oy does not check or modify the material it possibly receives through the Website, and is in no way responsible for any material sent to it through the Website. Codebay Oy has the right to hold public any material sent to it through the Website, and has no secrecy- or any other responsibility due to the material. By sending any material to Codebay Oy through the Website, the sender grants Codebay Oy the permanent, irrevocable and unrestricted right to copy, present, include into other material, show, modify, further develop, forward and distribute the material in question free of charge and without any obligations towards the user. The sender of the material also agrees and grants to Codebay Oy a right comparable to the aforementioned, to use and to exploit in its business activities in any way, any information, ideas, technology and other content contained in the aforementioned material.

Linking

The Website owned by Codebay Oy may contain links to the websites of other parties. The websites' own terms of use are applied to such websites and their use. Codebay Oy takes no responsibility for third parties' websites and their contents. Unless Codebay Oy expressly otherwise notifies, the company does in no way sponsor, support or otherwise give support to the linked pages in question, their content, use, or other related matters.

Copyright © Codebay Oy 2007. Codebay® and VPNease® are registered trademarks of Codebay Oy.

Document last updated: 27.8.2007.

Pricing

has a monthly per server license fee which depends on the number of concurrent end-user and site-to-site VPN connections as follows:

Number of concurrent end-user VPN connections
1-10 | 9€ / connection / month
11-100 | 8€ / connection / month
More than 100 | 7€ / connection / month

Number of site-to-site VPN connections
One site-to-site endpoint | 19€ / connection / month

Note: for a site-to-site connection, two servers and thus two licenses are required (for a total of 38€ per site-to-site connection).

Pricing details

Monthly license fee is determined by the highest fee during a calender month. When updating server license, the updated monthly fee recurs at the start of every following month. If the license fee increases, the difference between current and new monthly fee is invoiced for the current month. If the license fee decreases, the difference between current and new monthly fee is not returned.
Each serves requires a separate license, and discounts (for end-user VPN connection count) apply to each server license individually.
Prices do not include VAT, see Payment Options for VAT details.
Pricing is subject to change with 3 months notice.
Please see our partner pages for partner pricing information.

® PRIVACY POLICY

Privacy Policy

Codebay Oy

[Please click here to review full description of file in accordance with the Finnish Personal Data Act.]

Codebay Oy is committed to preserving the privacy of all users and customers of www.vpnease.com. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us.

By registering or placing an order on this site or by using the product, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information in accordance with Finnish Personal Data Act and under the terms of this policy.

Information that we collect from you

When you visit, register or order products on www.vpnease.com, you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name, contact details and credit or debit card information and technical data for delivery of your order. We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from messages you post to the website and e-mails or letters you send to us.

Our product collects technical data of the server it is installed into. This information does not include any personal data and it is collected for license management and error correction purposes only. Technical information collected includes license key, address of the server (IP address and port), installation identification data, version identification data and update method data. For bug fixing, error correction and development purposes we collect information of hardware/software equipment type and product errors ("watchdog process", for example re-booting in certain situations).

Our product does not collect or send us any information concerning users (such as user names or passwords), configuration or billing data (which is processed only in connection with user accounts of www.vpnease.com).

Use of your information

Your information will enable us to provide you with access to all parts of our site and to supply the goods or services you have requested. It will also enable us to bill you and to contact you where necessary concerning your orders. We will also use and analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our service and software products.

In particular, we may use your information to contact you for your views on our services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the site or our services. Further, where you have consented, we might also use your information to let you know about other products and services which we offer which may be of interest to you and we may contact you by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know.

Disclosure of your information

The information you provide to us will be stored and processed in accordance with the Finnish Personal Data Act. No personal information will be transferred to third parties or outside European Union except billing data, as may be applicable for our international customers. Countries outside the European Economic Area do not always have strong data protection laws. However, we will always take steps to ensure that your information is used by third parties in accordance with this policy.

Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent.

Cookies

Cookies are small amounts of information which we store on your computer. Unless you have indicated your objection when disclosing your details to us, our system may issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalise the content of the site for you. You may set up your computer to reject cookies. However, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site.

Security

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage.

Accessing and updating

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us.

Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the site and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.

Contact

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to info@vpnease.com.

Copyright © Codebay Oy 2007. Codebay® and VPNease® are registered trademarks of Codebay Oy.

Document last updated: 27.8.2007.

Product Comparison

Virtual Private Network (VPN) Overview

Virtual Private Network (VPN) products connect computers securely through insecure networks (such as the Internet), using encryption and other cryptographic techniques to secure data in transit. As a result, remote workers, customers, partners, and various company sites can be linked together securely, as if a secure "private network" existed between the parties. VPNs provide an extremely cost effective means of achieving secure connectivity, and have thus become popular in recent years.

VPN products typically provide two basic services:

Connecting remote workers and other individual users to a company network, which is often called "remote access VPN"
Connecting company or partner sites (networks) using a secure tunnel, which is often called "site-to-site VPN"

From a user perspective, remote access VPNs typically work like a modem connection: the remote access connection is opened, the user is authenticated using a username and a password, and a secure connection is created. User data traffic (in the form of IP data packets) can then be exchanged with the company network.

Site-to-site VPNs perform a similar function, but are autonomous. From user perspective they work similarly to a network router: data packets are sent to one site-to-site VPN device, which delivers them to the other site-to-site VPN device securely over the Internet, and the packets are then routed onwards. Many products provide one of these functions, while some products, like , provide both functions.

There are many VPN technologies in use, ranging from fully standard protocols (such as IPsec) to fully proprietary vendor-specific solutions (such as SSL VPNs). uses existing, reliable standards, and is based on the L2TP/IPsec VPN technology.

IPsec-based VPNs are the ideal technology for VPN connectivity, because they provide very high quality security (relied upon by banks and even military organizations), and they are packet based, which means that individual IP data packets are secured and transferred through the IPsec connection. This means that IPsec-based VPNs are fully transparent and are completely application independent. All the applications are protected automatically and can be used over the VPN connection. In particular, network services like Windows file sharing and Voice over IP (VoIP) are available without limitations.

Some other VPN technologies, like proprietary and SSL-based VPNs, are often application dependent. Many applications may not work without explicit support for the particular VPN solution.

— for Small and Medium Sized Businesses

has been designed to deliver the best available IPsec-based remote access and site-to-site VPN connectivity to small and medium sized businesses. The product has been designed with ease-of-use in mind: it is managed through a web-based interface, and built-in VPN client software provided by the operating system vendor is used without extra client software installation.

even provides fully automatic VPN client configuration for Windows XP and Windows Vista computers, which allows non-technical users to activate their VPN connection without administrative help.

The pricing model also suits small and medium sized businesses well. There is no fixed startup cost, but instead cost is capacity based (number of simultaneous remote access or site-to-site VPN connections). Finally, testing is free and requires no registration. Simply download and test.

Compare VPN Solutions

Feature | IPsec VPNs | SSL VPNs | Proprietary VPNs |
Security | IPsec and extensions | SSL and/or proprietary | Proprietary | L2TP/IPsec
Windows 2000 Client | Third party client | Third party client (1) | Third party client | Built-in
(Autoconf)
Windows XP Client | Third party client | Third party client (1) | Third party client | Built-in
(Autoconf)
Windows Vista Client | Third party client | Third party client (1) | Third party client | Built-in
(Autoconf)
Mac OS X Client | Third party client | Third party client (1) | Third party client | Built-in
Pocket PC / Windows Mobile Client | Typically no | Typically no (1) | Typically no | Built-in
Linux Client | Some | Typically no (1) | Some | Packaged client
Nokia Internet Tablet Client | Typically no | Typically no (1) | Typically no | Packaged client
Coexists with other VPN clients | Typically no | Typically no (1) | Typically no | Typically yes

(1) Third party client is needed for application neutral connections. Plain web access to company resources works with most browsers.

Security and Standards

Like most VPN products, authenticates the remote user by username and password, and protects all user data sent between the client and the server computers. This effectively prevents attackers from gaining access to data in transit, and allows an employee to access company resources even from untrusted networks. A VPN solution should be deployed in conjunction with supporting security measures, such as client firewall, anti-virus and anti-spam scanning, and hard disk encryption. Together, VPN and other security measures allow flexible access to your data, while protecting against external threats.

protects user data by encrypting data exchanged between the client and the server computers. uses the IPsec security protocol to ensure the highest possible security for encrypted user data. IPsec is a standard developed by the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF) and has been deployed commercially for almost 10 years. uses IPsec in conjunction with the L2TP protocol in a combination commonly referred to as L2TP/IPsec. See Encryption and Standards for details about cryptographic and compression algorithms.

Network Address Translation (NAT) is often a problem with many VPN solutions. supports the IPsec NAT traversal standard, allowing the product to work fully with all NAT and port forwarding devices. In particular, works correctly even when multiple client computers reside behind the same NAT device, a scenario which typically causes problems.

is an IPsec-based VPN product, which provides:

Easy and secure connectivity - connects employees and company sites to the corporate network through the Internet.
Very low support costs - uses the built-in VPN client of client operating systems, which eliminates compatibility problems and the need to install and update client software.
Application neutrality - supports all applications, including e-mail, Windows file shares, databases, VoIP, and videoconferencing.
Strong cryptography - uses the L2TP/IPsec VPN standard.

server software is installed on standard PC hardware and terminates VPN connections from the Internet. uses the built-in VPN clients of supported operating systems (XP, Vista, OS X, and others), so no software installation is required for clients. This removes the common VPN client software compatibility and stability problems, reducing support costs significantly compared to competing solutions.

is an easy and cost efficient, yet reliable and secure solution. Taking into use requires no fixed fees. You only pay a monthly fee, starting from 9€ / month, based on connection capacity.

See product documentation to find out more about , or try the product free for 30 days (installation and testing takes about 45 minutes). You can also send us a question if you don't find the information you're looking for.